Okay, so I'm going to hand over to G for the first bit of the call.
Thank you.
Okay then, so today we're doing some new year goal setting intro.
So by the end of this workshop, we will have the tools and understanding to set
clear actionable
goals aligned with our values and long term vision.
Setting goals is important because they provide direction, focus and motivation
.
Goals give you a clear vision of what you want to achieve, which help you
prioritise
your time and energy.
They also break down larger tasks into manageable steps, making progress
measurable and keeping
you on track.
Additionally, achieving goals builds confidence and a sense of accomplishments
which can lead
to further success.
So I thought I'd start off by asking, what is one goal that you achieved last
year that
you're proud of?
We can have a minute or two to think about this and we can just think about it
to ourselves
or if you would like, we can also share as well with each other.
So just take a minute to think about what is one goal or even what are a couple
of goals,
if more come to mind that you achieved last year that you're proud of and write
this down
on the top of your paper as well, please.
Thank you.
It's cute watching on your concentration faces.
Okay, I'll give it one more minute and then we'll see if anyone would like to
share.
Okay then, does anyone want to share what they achieved last year that they're
proud
of?
Yeah, I will.
Yeah, I think coming back to coming after two years because I've suffered
chronic pain
so it's to do something for myself and realising that well, I've written a
multi-streaming doesn't
work.
It's too tiring and too time consuming just to concentrate on one site.
Okay, perfect, lovely.
And yeah, I agree about the multi-streaming.
It can't be hard and I think with this to be really successful is to connect
with your
clients.
So it's hard to connect with them if you're trying to connect with a couple and
one goal.
So yeah, I think that's a really smart move that you've done there and I knew
before.
Thank you for sharing.
Does anyone else want to share?
Last year I got married and my husband is a very big supporter of me coming.
In fact, I think he's my biggest fan, even though he calls himself my only fan.
Yeah, I'm proud of myself getting married and being up in public because when
you're
on camera, even though you're being viewed by the public, you're in a selfism.
So I was able to get out of my comfort zone with that and be in public in front
of my
friends and family.
Oh, I love that.
That's honestly such a big story.
Is it amazing?
Congratulations.
So lovely.
Thank you.
Does anyone else want to share?
I will share one.
So I was thinking about what I said on this call last year because we always do
this call
by the way in January, so it's quite nice because we have some of the same
people coming
back sometimes or watching it back and thinking about the goals they made the
year before.
So I know that when my goals last year was about body confidence and it was
about like,
yeah, because I've just gone through such a journey with fitness and I'm in a
lot of
places where I don't wear very much.
So I was like holding myself to account to always be like this Amazon goddess,
which
I can be for about one day of the month if I'm lucky.
So yeah, my goal and proud of that I've met is actually that I feel so
comfortable in
my body.
And when I put a bit of weight on, I'm still at King parties in my latex,
actually loving
the fact that I'm showing off my roles or whatever.
And equally, I'm loving it when I've got a bit of this fixed packing and
feeling that
way as well.
So yeah, I'm proud of myself for kicking that finally after so long.
Yeah, it's hard, isn't it, like the judgment that we put on ourselves sometimes
and no
matter how much from the outside people tell you, oh, you look amazing this
start.
It needs to, it's not going to resonate, it needs to come from a vein.
So I'm so glad to hear that you've overcome that finally and you're feeling
good about
your body, which you sure it's because you are just insane.
You are amazing.
Thank you.
Does anyone else want to share before we move on?
No, okay, that's absolutely fine, let's head to the next slide, please Elle.
And later on from what Elle was just saying about, we do this every year.
I went through all of the previous goals and workshops and selected some of the
best content
and put it onto this.
So this is kind of like an upgraded version of all the previous years that we
've done.
I've tweaked some of it and I've added new bits.
So if anyone's done this before and you see some of the same things coming up,
that's
why.
But yes, this is success versus happiness.
So when I was planning this call, I was looking online for inspiration.
And I landed on a website that suggested an exercise to ask the group what does
success
look like to you.
But then I realised that we also need to consider happiness too, as a lot of
the time, people
less society deemed successful might not be happy.
And to me, to be completely successful is to be happy.
So this is a great question to ask yourself and to properly think about it as
you might
deem success different when you realise that you need to bring happy into the
equation.
Because the word success, first of all, made me think about Korean finance, but
then the
more thought about it, I began to realise that to me success is a lot more than
that.
Success is being happy, success is having freedom, it's being able to live on
my schedule, and
that's what success looks like to me.
Realising what success means to you will give you more of an idea of what
direction to take
your life before doing this exercise.
You may have told yourself that success is getting a high paying job, for
example.
But then when you sit and think about it, you might actually realise it wouldn
't make
you happy.
And it might mean that you're financially successful.
But then it might mean you're working long hours, you're not able to see your
family and
know you'll have no time for yourself, you're stressed, you're tired all the
time.
So you could work hard for years to get to this position.
But then once you're there, you realise you don't actually want to be there.
So with that being said, let's take a couple of minutes to have a think about
what success
looks like to us while considering our happiness.
And we can also write this down.
So we'll spend five minutes on this one because I think this one is really
important.
I'll set the timer now on my phone for five minutes.
Hey, do our new joiner.
So I'll just talk you through what we've done already.
We've written down on a piece of paper what a goal that we achieved last year
that we're
proud of.
And now we are taking a look at success versus happiness.
So have a think about what success looks like to you while considering your
happiness.
And you can write that down also.
So I want you guys to think deeply about this one and try and hit it from all
angles.
There's no right or wrong answer and you could have multiple answers with
multiple meanings.
So yes, just think a little think about that one.
Okay.
We've got two.
Okay, we've got two minutes left so finish this one.
Okay, we've got two minutes left so we've got two minutes left so finish this
one.
Okay, we've got two minutes left so finish this one.
Okay, then we'll move on to the next slide.
I won't ask you to share this one because this one is quite personal so we won
't share
this one.
And if you guys aren't finished, you can always just go back at the end of the
call and, you
know, finish off the things here and there but for now we'll head on to the
next slide.
Okay, so what do you want for 2025?
Okay, so now I would like you to make a list of absolutely everything that you
want to
achieve this year, big or small, it doesn't matter, just write it down.
So for example, you could write I want to make a deposit on a house or I want
to end
the shower with a cold rinse.
So obviously this is a really big one and then this is just also a small one so
literally
everything that you want to achieve this year.
And so we'll have a few minutes to do that one.
So what you need to achieve to bring you to true happiness but what you need to
do this
week to tie up a loose end and what could you achieve this year that will
change your
life, spend a few minutes on this.
Okay.
So think about absolutely everything that you would like, even if it's
unimaginable to
you right now, putting it out there, putting it a paper, putting it into your
mind, you
know, that's creating the momentum for it to potentially happen, even if it's
something
that, you know, you think is out of your reach at the moment, still write it
down, still
put that into your mind that you want that and you will start to attract
opportunities
for that to actually happen.
So don't, um, don't like cut yourself short, I ain't put the straws.
We'll spend one more minute on this.
Okay.
Let's move on to the next part of the exercise.
Okay, so now that we have the list of everything that we would like to achieve,
we will organise
it.
So we will do this by writing one, two or three next to each goal.
So number one represents a goal that can be easily achieved with not a lot of
effort.
So, you know, I don't know if it might, one of mine would, for example, would
be to go
sew that pair of knickers that I need to sew, that's not, I need to go sew
those.
So obviously that's just small one that I can do that doesn't take long.
And then you'll write a number two next to the goals that require a lot more
time and
effort.
And then finally, you'll write number three next to the goals that will take a
long time.
It might take six months to a year to achieve these ones that you can do that
now.
Okay.
Everyone can you hit the next for me please.
Thank you.
Okay.
So before we share, I'd like everyone to just pick one or two of the goals that
you wrote
number one next to.
So the ones that don't take long to do and make a promise to yourself to
achieve them
by the end of this week because basically, if you're going to get this done by
the end
of this week, it's going to make you feel motivated to achieve your more, your
more
like time consuming goals because it will basically install competence in you
that you
can do whatever you want.
I don't know about you girls, but sometimes I'll have medium, small tasks that
stay on
my to do list for weeks and weeks and weeks and I procrastinate on them.
But then once I start to do them and, you know, I start getting these little
things
done.
I just get this energy and motivation from nowhere and I'm just getting so much
So I think that it's always good instead of looking at the goals that are like
these,
you know, huge goals that are going to take months and months and months to do
to get
us in the, you know, in the swing of things, it's good to get a few of these
smaller things
done.
And then you start to think to yourself, Oh, actually, I can, I can do this,
you know?
So pick one or two of your goals that are just the small ones and make a note
to actually
get them done this week.
And then we can check in with each other next week and let each other know that
we actually
done this and then we can start conquering our bigger goals.
So would anyone like to share some things that they want to achieve this year?
Sharing it with a group as well also makes you accountable.
So it'll just make it even more real for you and, you know, even more like, you
're more
likely to actually do it.
So who wants to share?
I'll share.
Sorry, I'm having a wee, that's why I've asked her my video.
And as you know, like my goals every year on this have always been like quite
big.
I don't know if you can see me now, can you see me?
Yeah.
And I've always like achieved everything and I'm not just saying that like you
girls know
I literally have.
So this year it was kind of nice to not have like massive goals if you know
what I mean.
So one of mine, not massive goals because they're still important goals to me
but you
know, like the last couple of years I've had like really big expectations and
really
big goals and I have done them.
One of mine was to just empty my washing pile by the end of the week.
Like I know that sounds ridiculous and my husband is like no chance.
But just to have like an empty washing basket for once in my life would be like
a really
big achievement to me this week because I feel like it's been months since that
's happened.
Another one was to have organised puppets and yeah, like my covers, they're
just opening
when I want to cry and I want to shut the doors again.
So that was another one that I thought could be done pretty quickly.
And yeah, that was like obviously got bigger ones as well but there's two of
mine that
I think I should possibly choose on the end of the week.
Love that.
Thank you for sharing Sammy.
But honestly, how are you going to feel when it's done?
Yeah.
And then I'll be like right now I'm going to do the next one so I'm going to do
the next
time.
Exactly.
It's going to be a snowball effect.
I love that.
Yeah.
You want to see a picture of your puppets?
And also your.
From basket.
Oh.
So anyone that doesn't know just like that's so like I always love these things
because
I love hearing how people meet their goals over the years.
Sammy has literally when she says like she's met goals that she wants to meet.
It's like buying her dream house and like stuff like that.
I live my dream life now like a little bit like oh, I'm like oh, what's the fun
?
Yeah, literally.
So it's so lovely to hear that because it's like just so nice that we can come
back here
every year and see those things happening for more people.
It's lovely.
And you can all do it 100%.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Thank you for sharing Sammy.
You're welcome.
Are you those organised cupboards?
Can I start?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hi, everyone.
So nice to see everyone's faces for the first time.
This is so special to me because I was kind of like struggling for such a long
time to
find a remote income and stuff like that.
I met G in Copenhagen and I was randomly living there during COVID.
I started teaching English just because I wanted to live there.
I'm from Brazil.
I'm originally a journalist.
I moved to Ireland like work as a waitress.
So like my life, I love travelling.
I love living in other places.
And I was always like getting stuck in jobs that I didn't really want but
because I wanted
to stay in the place and I don't know.
Last year kind of started doing OnlyFans like really slow low keys too.
And I remember about the webcam and I got in touch with you girls and literally
like
I I was almost crying like last year.
One of my goals from last year was to end the year with like this amount of
money.
It was not even much.
And I had nothing.
I own money for my friends.
This is like December.
I own money.
I was living my friend's house and literally like I started camping and in two
weeks I
managed to pay my friends back.
I made the money that I wanted like since the beginning of the year to have.
And now I'm like planning to go to Asia.
That's my goal this year.
I put number two because I just need to buy tickets so I need to work more.
But yeah, I'm super excited.
And I love that like we write down paper and sometimes we don't believe in
ourselves.
But when actually when you put effort and you believe that you can do it, start
with
the small tiny tasks like and it's so true.
We start like every day I do small goals and like I have to wake up into yoga
and cook
and take a shower and I'm going to do like cam for three hours or cam until I
get this
money and you actually can do it.
And it's really amazing.
And one of my other biggest biggest goals as I said, I'm a journalist.
I've been writing a book and I was planning to finish last year, but so many
things happen
in accordance and this year it's my plan to finish this book and yeah.
So that's what I want and to make a lot of fucking money.
Oh, thank you so much for sharing honestly, like just my smile, like listening
to that.
Honestly, I just want my heart so much.
I'm so happy that you that you're here with us and you're able to, you're able
to pay
your friends back so fast and all of this stuff is just amazing.
And I was like, uh, things are changing and they're good because so many shit
happened
for me like a couple of years.
And now I'm like, oh, it's nice, like it's nice to think only what I want and I
can do
everything I want.
Good.
You can.
I love that.
I hope that we dance together again soon.
Yeah, please let's meet in Asia.
Yeah.
100%.
Oh, I love that.
Thank you so much.
Well, yeah, you mentioned about like every day you have your small goals, you
know, like
take a shower.
Do you get this that I do exactly the same, like I have my list on my phone
here and I
have like Thursday and then all my things I want to do and then like, you know,
I take
off that I've done it and then even like every day I've got Friday.
So then things that I know need to be done each day, I'll just write it all
down.
And then it's actually so satisfying to just be like, tick I've done that one.
So even if it's something small, like you said, like take a shower or do your
yoga or whatever
it is, I think it is important to like list it out.
And then, you know, you can just take it off your list and it's done.
And sometimes if you don't have that list, it doesn't get done, you know.
So in, yeah, love that.
I think also it's keeping it up as well, making sure you keep on, keep on track
.
I think it's good to have this group because we can all keep each other
accountable as
well.
Yeah.
And if someone's having a bad day, we can just, like, can I just, like, I just
need to
get this out.
Can I talk to someone?
There's always going to be someone there.
And then once you got that negative bit out, you can, like, that's gone, you
can just get
back to it.
So it's always nice to be able to talk to people and have them want good things
for
you as well.
100% love that.
Yeah.
Thank you for your contributions in the group as well, because it's so nice
when new people
come in and like to see them chat in and, you know, we love to see people just
chatting.
There's been some lovely friendships made, well, for us and so many.
So it's nice to see new people coming in and chatting with each other.
It's the first meeting that I've come to, but I've done with you guys for quite
a few
months now.
It's just been like timing.
It's just not been right, but yeah, this is, I've been so stoked for this first
night.
Okay, would one more person like to share before we move on or?
Yeah, I think for me, it's going to be getting my laptop set up.
That'll be the first thing, I can't do anything without that.
Getting my software set up and growing my clients.
That's going to be mine for the end of the foot, my goal for the end of the
week.
Perfect.
Amazing.
Okay, so let us know when your laptop's all set up.
I will definitely.
Yeah.
Yeah, of that.
Thank you for sharing.
Okay then.
Okay, so now that we know what we want to achieve, let's create a plan.
So we're going to use the smart goals model.
Some of you will have done this before as we've done this on previous calls.
I think I was looking at different like models that we could have used because
there's different
things you can use to break down the goals, but I do believe this is the best
one.
Okay, so let's set a plan in motion.
So we will do this with some of the bigger goals as we don't really need to use
this
for the small ones because they don't require much thought or time or effort, a
lot of the
small ones, but some of our bigger ones definitely do and they can look quite
daunting if you're
just looking at the huge goal that you need to achieve.
So if we break it down, it really does show that it's very realistic for this
to be achieved.
So go through some of your bigger goals and break them down to make sure they
are smart
goals.
So we'll do this with two or three and then after the call, you can do it for
the rest
of them.
So you'll have a plan for all of your goals and you'll know exactly how to do
it.
So smart goals are specific, measurable, achievable, relevant and time bound.
That's what it stands for.
So I've done an example for you guys and then you can go through and do it on
your own.
So for specific, you want to use as much detail as possible and be clear about
what you want.
For example, I want to buy a five bedroom, two bathroom, the touch house with a
garden
located in Liverpool.
So that's obviously very specific, measurable.
So this is going to be the quantity or how you'll define the progress for
measurement.
So I would track my progress by noting down my savings to make sure I'm on
track.
This is like this is going back to the house goal.
This is just an example.
So achievable.
So how will we do it?
So you want to set a realistic goal based on your resources.
So I will achieve this by sticking to a money savings plan while searching real
estate websites
for my dream home.
I will also look on housing auctions for the good deal.
So relevant.
So you want to make sure your goal is relevant in your life right now and it
aligns with
your broader values and long-term vision.
So yes, this is relevant in my life as I've wanted to buy a house for years and
now I'm
finally in a position to do so.
Time bound.
So when and so when will you do it basically?
So you can set a deadline to help focus your efforts and track progress.
So for my example, it would be I want to buy a house within the next six to
eight months.
If I stay on track with my savings goal, I should be able to.
So before smart goals, my goal would have been I want to buy a house.
But now that we've looked at the smart goals model and broken it down, my goal
now becomes
I want to buy a five bedroom, two bathrooms, a touch house with a garden
located in Liverpool
within the next six to eight months, through tracking my savings and keeping an
eye on
the housing market, I can make this possible.
So as you can see the goal comes from just a very broad answer to then you're
basically
like breaking it all down and giving yourself the steps on how to do it.
So we will do this now.
I will give you guys five or so minutes to do this.
If anyone has any questions, please ask and yeah, we will share at the end.
So by setting a clear plan of action that you know you are able to follow will
make a
huge difference to whether you were able to achieve your goals or not.
I'll give another example.
So let's say the goal is to lose weight so the goal could be I want to lose
weight.
To make it a smart goal you would say I want to lose 10 pounds within the next
four weeks
by eating healthy and training twice every week.
So the goal then becomes a lot more realistic because you've set yourself a
time frame,
you've know how much you want to lose, you know how you're going to do it, when
you're
going to do it and so yeah I think the smart goals model is really good because
it just
makes your goal seem way more achievable.
While you're writing this I'll tell you guys about the 1% rule maybe you've
already heard
about it but this is something that when I'm feeling overwhelmed if I'm looking
at something
I need to do and it seems as though it's quite a big task that it's quite hard
to get there.
I think of the 1% rule and the 1% rule basically just means a 1% improvement
every day so instead
of looking at something like I've got this huge, huge task to do if you think
okay this
is a big task I need to do but if today I take this one step tomorrow I take
this step
the next day I take this step and then gradually you'll get there by doing 1
step every day
so 1% every day so that's a nice way to look at things sometimes when you have
a big task
it kind of makes me feel a lot less daunting.
[ Silence ]
We'll spend one more minute on this and if you're not finished like again once
the call
is over you can go back through at the end and finish it off or do the smart
goals for
the rest of your goals.
[ Silence ]
Okay then we'll finish this up now.
Does anyone want to share one of their goals and how they've made it a smart
goal?
Yeah, I'd like to type model to abroad this year so measurable we'll be working
more
hours a day once I get started.
I'm looking at holiday deals, well it's achievable and I'm looking at three
months.
Yeah amazing, where would you like to take your daughter?
Spain, nowhere too far because she doesn't travel very well because she's
disabled but
she hasn't been abroad yet and she's 13 so.
Oh nice, it's beautiful.
And I just want to get back into coming again, I absolutely love it.
Yeah, that's my main goal.
Yeah, what's your own persona on webcam?
Pardon?
What's your persona on webcam, like how do you?
Milk mainly.
Yeah, I love that.
40, I, just as I am to be honest, just me playing with toys and stuff like that
, yeah.
Okay, well I've got a look with the quest to take your daughter away, I'm sure
to have
your own.
Thank you.
Okay.
I've got one and so I want to buy a house as at least three bedrooms, two
toilets, garden
and the garage in the worthy area.
I'll try this by completing my savings bills each month by spending more time
online earning
the money and looking at a stage on websites.
And I want to be in a position to buy this house by my 28th birthday in 363
days, so,
yeah, amazing.
Good look with that.
It's obviously a really big goal, so when you achieve that, that feels amazing.
So yeah, good look with that one.
And happy belated birthday.
Thank you, I'm 27 now.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Susan.
Okay, well done girls, so organizing your goals into smart goals.
We're going to move on now to some visualization and manifestation and I'm
going to pass you
over to Elle for this one.
Okay, so let's talk about visualization and manifestation and then I'm going to
do a
little visualization, a little exercise for anybody that wants to do it.
It'll just be a couple of minutes that it'll help us to bring some of these
goals to life
a little bit more in our bodies, rather than just thinking about it with our
minds.
So we've looked at what will make us happy whilst driving for success, we've
laid out
everything wants to achieve and made a plan of action, so let's make it feel a
bit more
real.
So manifestation is the process of bringing something into reality through
focused thoughts,
belief and intention is often linked to the idea that by visualising or aff
irming a goal,
you align your mindset and your actions to make that goal more likely to happen
.
Well some people view manifestation as a way to attract opportunities or
outcomes by focusing
positively on them.
Other people see it more as a self empowerment tool that helps to clarify
desires, increase
motivation and encourage proactive behaviour.
So however much you are into this, there's nothing negative really that can
come is there
from holding a belief about your goals and giving your goals your attention,
giving your
intention, your attention and your action, those three things are really what
manifestation
is made up of.
And yeah, there's no denial that if something is constantly in your mind every
day, that
you'll be looking for things that are going to back up that goal that you've
got, maybe
you'll be having conversations with people and they might say, "Oh well I know
about this"
or it seeps into your life, into your conversations, it may even, I sort of
give the example that
I used to sort of say that I was a therapist, at places where I didn't really
know anyone
before I was really a therapist because I was kind of like speaking it into the
world
and then people started to kind of see me that way and then I finished my
training after
so many years and I felt like I'd kind of like brought it into my reality in so
many
different ways before it was a reality.
So that's manifestation and visualization can be something that we can do which
is a part
of manifestation which can just be a lovely thing to do, a lovely exercise as
well and
we'll do a little bit of it together.
So manifestation often works best when combined with practical efforts of
course and realistic
goal setting as we've just done.
It's not just about hoping for something to happen, it's about creating a
mental environment
where opportunities can be recognised and acted upon.
Yeah, I, again, I always feel like saying this when we're talking about like
manifestation
and things that had used to have a funny relationship with it because, you know
, there are people
that sort of band it about and don't understand that it's a privilege to be in
a position,
isn't it, to be able to manifest some of the things that you want.
Everybody has that privilege and, you know, we need a certain level of safety
before we
can even consider success and happiness and what those things look like.
Which is kind of like, you know, when Sammy was talking earlier about the big
goals that
she met, I was feeling the same way like webcam enabled me to meet the big
goals of, you know,
I have a small cottage but it's literally my safety and my home and I bought it
with my
money and so, so yeah, just a side note that, you know, these visualizations
and manifestations,
if you aren't in a really difficult position, safety, you know, we need to have
the safety
to do the visualization and the manifestation and everything else, so it's a
privilege to
be doing these things.
But whatever position you're in, it's really nice to have a space like this
where we can
come together and do a bit of visualization together, so let's do it.
So what I would recommend, if you want to, because we're going to be closing
our eyes,
so if it helps you to feel more comfortable, you can put your camera off at
this point,
just so you know that nobody's going to see you and you're completely on your
own, quickly
leave it on if you want whatever feels comfortable for you, we're just going to
take a few minutes,
so we're going to come back a few minutes and all you need to do during this
time is
just make sure you're nice and comfortable wherever you're sat, if you're
sitting down,
just make sure it's something that you're somewhere you're going to be able to
sit for
a few minutes or you can even lie down if you want to and we're going to, if
you feel
comfortable too, just gently close your eyes and all you have to do is listen
along.
All you have to do is listen along.
If at any point, you know, it feels a bit intense or it gets a bit much, you
can open
your eyes, just look around the room, sense yourself in the room, but it's
going to be
a really chill, really chill few minutes of just bringing some of this to lie.
So to start with, we've gently closing our eyes and we're just going to take
some nice
big deep breaths together, so however this feels comfortable and natural to you
, I like
to breathe in through my nose, for a few counts, holding, pausing at the top
for a
couple of moments and then doing a nice big exhale, so we'll just continue
taking some
nice big deep breaths together like this and as we breathe, we want to feel the
rise
and fall of the body, so just noticing how it feels as that air enters and then
leaves
your body and you might like to just let your shoulders drop on your next exh
ale.
Just noticing any tension in your body, any stiffness and just giving yourself
permission
to rest a little further, relax a little more.
So there might be thoughts or sensations that come up and try to grab your
attention, but
we're not going to check into them, we can notice them and just bring our
attention
back to our breathing and if it helps to bring your attention inwards, you
might like to
just notice any contact points between you and where you're sitting, so maybe
feel your
bumps out on the chair or your feet on the floor, just feel where things are
supporting
you and just let yourself know that there's nothing you need to do in this
moment, there's
no expectation, no agenda, there's no way you need to be, just giving yourself
permission
to be in this moment, just listening along just for a couple of minutes.
Now in your mind's eye, I'd like you to visualise as clearly as you can
yourself, I'd like you
to visualise yourself sitting in a nice, comfortable and peaceful room, so just
imagine what this
comfortable and peaceful room looks like to you, so it's somewhere that you
feel safe,
so it may be somewhere that you've been before, it may be an imaginary place
and I want you
to imagine yourself sat in this room, so how does it feel, where exactly are
you sitting,
what colours can you see around you, what textures can you feel in this room
that you're
sitting in, and I want you to imagine that you're sitting in this lovely room
that you
visualised a year from now and you're thinking about the goals that you've tick
ed off this
list that we've made, so just bringing into your mind some of these goals that
you've
been writing down and how it's going to feel when you're sitting in this room a
year from
now, just acknowledging the goals that you've ticked off, and bring that into
focus a little
more, perhaps think about what you're wearing as you're sitting there, this
person that's
achieved these goals, what's your demeanor, how are you sitting and how do you
feel about
yourself, are there any emotions you're feeling about having met these goals,
and perhaps
just breathing in that sense of accomplishment and that pride, and just
acknowledging that
you're on track, that you've made some commitments to yourself and you've made
them happen, perhaps
you might have had obstacles along the way but you overcame them, you stayed
focused.
Now as you're inviting in those feelings, just notice any resistance to this
vision
that you might have had, so any thoughts or sensations that are blocking you,
anything
that have come up that have made it difficult, I wonder if you can just release
those, just
release those blockages to make space for your new life.
And as you visualise yourself a year from now in this room that you've created,
I'd like
you to imagine yourself just standing up and going about your day, what will
your day look
like a year from now having met your goals, think about the people, how you
feel around
those people, the things you're going to do, maybe the work, or the things you
're going
to create, just solidifying this image of yourself.
So when we're ready we can take another nice big deep breaths just to get us
back into
our body again and back into this present moment and if it feels natural to you
, you
might want to have a stretch, have a nice big stretch and gently open your eyes
and just
sense to yourself in the room again, so just taking a few moments, have a look
around
you, it's something like this, so it reminds me of CBT that I do every day.
Oh really, yeah, it's really nice to do something a bit different isn't it
sometimes and just
really relaxing, yeah, yeah.
It's not often that we just allow ourselves some inner attention, so just to
stop and just
to bring your attention inwards, you know, it's really important.
I hope you enjoyed that, ladies, how did we all find it, does anyone want to
talk about
how they found that?
I found it quite interesting because I thought I was going to be manifesting
wealth and just
big pieces of gordy furniture because in my head, that's what success is meant
to be,
but really I just imagined myself being happier, more confident, walking around
the house,
like I owned it and having my nieces over like cake and just like more family
time rather
than like more financial success, it was more emotional success.
Yeah, that's lovely, thank you, thank you for that, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
When we were talking about the success, my thing that I wrote down was time,
success
to me is time, like time with loved ones, time for yourself, time to create and
express
and, yeah, just, yeah, that's a nice image of you in your house with your nie
ces.
Does anybody else want to share a little bit before we meet before?
Yeah, I'd like to share, yeah, thank you so much, I really like this practice
and it was
very important for me of what you said before about safety because my goals are
safety goals,
so it's not like some big dreams about like achieving basic safety for me and
my child,
and I felt safe during this manifestation and visualization, just safe and calm
and just
kind of like quiet, just normal because I also had a few difficult years and to
arrive
at that level of just calmness and just normalcy and safety would be amazing.
So I really enjoyed it that I kind of like, I don't have to kind of like jump
over my
head and like imagine anything, I don't know, which is, I don't know, totally
out of reach,
but to achieve that safety that would be actually amazing and it feels much
more realistic as
well actually, yeah, yeah, so thank you.
I feel like in fact, in the same old voice, row is so calming and I felt like
so safe
in this little, I mean my bedroom and my husband is next to me and he watches
some terrible
film, the dog snoring, but I just suddenly felt like really quiet and calm and
also like
a little bit emotional when he was talking because I thought what safe spaces
has been
to me for like the last couple of years and every time we've done this, it's
been different
for me and a different like mindset and yeah, and it just said like life moves
on and you
grow in and yeah, your mindset changes and I thought I'd just start a bit
emotional when
you were talking and it was really nice and I felt really calm even though
there's quite
a bit of noise about it, so thank you for that.
Oh, thank you, thank you, both of you, thank you Maria for feeding back as well
, yeah,
I think that's what I love about this call is that you get to see the
progression, you
get to see people, yeah, and you know, I certainly found my safety through this
work, I would
not have done anywhere near anything like God have a house like, you know,
where I'm
from, that doesn't happen, like you know, that's just unheard of, so yeah, I
think that yeah,
finding safety is just webcam, it can just be a lifeline, can't it, so thank
you so much
for sharing, that's so lovely to hear and it's so lovely how we just all
connect to it in
different ways and I feel you as well, Sami, I really do like earlier doing the
exercise
and stuff, I'm like, wow, I'm actually in such a privileged position that there
's nothing
that I need, need, need, you know, my goals are all about giving back and so
yeah, that's
lovely, that's lovely and it's so nice that we're all on this journey together,
ladies,
I can't wait to see some of you next year and hopefully see you, you know, in a
different
place and having achieved some of those goals, so thank you for doing that with
me, I always
enjoy doing those because it's just a nice exercise, isn't it, it's calming for
me as
well, okay, well this feels a bit like very different energies and it diving
into money
mindset, I didn't know that this was the next slide, just Georgia, do you want
me to
go through this or do you want to go through it because you, yeah, sure, I've
got the notes
written on it, but if there's anything extra you want to add then go ahead, but
honestly
thank you so much for that previous slide, the exercise well, honestly, I could
listen
to your voice all day, you make me feel so calm and yeah, just visualising
where I'm
going to be when achieving my biggest goal this year, it just brings me so much
happiness,
so thank you so much for that, but yes, moving on to money mindset, like you
said, a bit
of a different energy, but this was on one of the previous goals that we'd done
and like
I said I went through all of the old PowerPoint from the previous goal set and
workshops and
selected some of the best bits and although this is not goal setting, let's say
I thought
why not have something like this in there because it's always good to make our
mindset
around money really good, so here are some things that we can look at with
money mindset
so sorry, I'm trying to govern myself, but I'm a bit like still in the
meditation, okay
so looking at the bigger picture, so by this we mean looking at like what you
have, so
a lot of us, hopefully all of us here, we have a roof over our head, we have a
bed to
sleep in, we have clothes, food, water, so it's good to get in a state of
gratitude for
all of the abundance that we already have, these basic things, sometimes we can
take
for granted, but to have all of the things I've just mentioned, put us in a
really privileged
position compared to a lot of people in this world who don't have these basic
things, so
yeah, whenever we're feeling like our money mindset isn't great, if we're not
feeling
good about money or that kind of a thing, we can just look at the bigger
picture and
maybe we're like well actually I do already have a lot, so it's always good to
take a
step back and look at that.
I think, do you mind if I step in on that one as well Jay, I think also for me
looking
at that, like looking at the bigger picture can mean like looking at your
earnings, your
cam earnings over a month rather than looking at them, because I know like
especially at
times when I've really needed that money and I've had a bad day, like it's easy
to spiral
and be like oh my god, this is not working anymore or I don't know, whatever,
but then
when you kind of like zoom out and look at, you know, I've gone like the credit
activity
and just put in the month and look at the month and what I've actually earned,
I'll be like
oh wow, like usually it's like okay, yeah I'm doing okay and I think like, but
anyone who's
neurodivergent like me, you can get, you can get, you can hone in and get stuck
on like
oh my god, I haven't made money to me today so like, you know, get really pan
icky about
it and forget to zoom out and actually, you know, a few hours later actually
just after
one client it's okay, so yeah, I think that's what that means for me as well.
Yeah definitely, that's definitely a good thing to do for sure on those days
when you're
not as busy and that kind of leads into the next point with which is check what
money
you've got coming in, so sometimes you could be worrying about, you know, not
making much
money at the moment, but then for the people who've got jobs as well as cam,
you know,
you can take a look and be like, well actually I might not be, have much right
now, but I
know that every Monday I get paid this amount, so then at least putting you in
the mindset
of abundance, like, you know, you've got that coming in.
Another thing you can do is keep cash in your purse and I think it was you L
that told me
about this one, you could draw out like 50 or 100 pounds or you know, however
much and
just keep it in your purse and when you're out and about, do whatever you're
doing with
your day, you see something on the shelf that you like that you would want, you
think you
can think to yourself, I have the money to get that, maybe you're not going to
buy it
that day, but just knowing that you have the money to buy that, it switches
your mindset
from, oh I can't have that thing to, actually I can't have that, I'm not going
to pay just
it right now, but it starts to make you realise all of the things that you can
have and it
will make you feel more positive about money, is there anything you want to add
to that
one L?
You know that's actually an Abraham Hicks tip, which is, yeah, a manifestation
tip, which
yeah I like, because I had to really like heal my relationship with money for
years it took
me, I think that was on my goal list for like about three years at least, after
I actually
got into a position where I was like safe and had enough money, you know, so
that's something
that really helped me and yeah, it doesn't have to be like 100 pounds, it can
be 20 pounds
because you can be like, you know, walking past, I was going to say Starbucks,
I hate
Starbucks, but you know, in example you walk past Starbucks and think like I
can get myself
like a really creamy lovely coffee, like it's about the pleasure and having it,
like it's
in my back pocket, like walking past that thing, or I could get on that bus, or
I could
grab a taxi now, or even if it's money that you need, so you know you're not
going to
spend it because you need it, just putting that thought to the side and being
like, I could,
I could rather than, I can't all the time, you know. And yeah, I really liked
that one,
that actually did shift things a bit for me when I could feel like I could, it
was a choice
that I wasn't doing it, I could, because I had the money on me.
Yeah, I love that one. And it kind of also leads into this next one of noticing
limit
and beliefs. And so noticing if you have any limiting beliefs surrounding money
and working
out letting them go, I like to do rituals of letting go with limiting beliefs
by writing
it out on the paper, whatever that limiting belief is. Of course, this doesn't
need to
be just limiting beliefs around money, it can be any limiting beliefs. And
especially
when it's a full moon, it's a good time to do this. I think the next full moon
is on
one day, it might be a good time to do that, or you can do it anytime,
obviously, but if
you like to work with the energies of the moon, you can do it then. And so you
can write it
down. And then all of the things that all of your limiting beliefs, and then
you can
take a moment of meditation of letting it go. And then you can burn the paper,
obviously
do this safely, do it outdoors somewhere. And you can burn the paper and just
watch your
limiting beliefs just disappear away. Obviously, it's not that easy, it's not
just going to
go just like that. Like L just said, one of his strong limiting beliefs, he
took a year
to let go of, and it probably took him many different exercises to get there.
But yeah,
this is one that you can do, and it will even if it doesn't fully go with that
one exercise,
you'll definitely be one step closer to letting it go. So yeah, that's
something you can do
as well. And another thing is never tell yourself you can't have something like
L just mentioned
then, instead of saying you can't say, well, I could, I'm just choosing not to
in this
moment, but I definitely could have it. And if you really want it, then you
will have
it at some stage. And finally, believe you deserve it, because you do whatever
we want
in this life we definitely deserve. So if you believe that you deserve it, the
opportunities
will flow for you to bring that to you. And so yeah, there was just a little
bit on money
mindset. Is there anything you wanted to add? I think just on the like noticing
limiting
beliefs, obviously, there's so much in there as a therapist, like there's there
's so many
reasons why we might have those. I think just being mindful, not to shame
yourself, like
sometimes when we try to let go of something, we're shaming ourselves out of
doing the
thing, which is not letting go of it at all. Like, when you're letting go of
something
or wait, when you're intentionally trying to come away from something, it's
more about
feeling compassion for the part of you that had to feel that way. You know,
feeling compassion
for the part of you that had to feel like you couldn't have things or that went
through
experiences where you didn't have things, you know, that had to see other
people have
things maybe or whatever. Like, you can, you don't need to shame yourself out
of having
those thoughts. You can notice them and feel compassion for yourself. But okay,
that's
not reality anymore. That's where letting that go now. You know, so I think it
's important
to have like a sort of self nurturing way of doing any of this stuff,
especially like
when it comes to a money mindset thing. Thank you. Thank you, Jay, for that.
Okay, so yeah,
we're going to finish up with just, not very long, we won't take much more of
your time,
just a little bit of talking about our year in review, because it's really nice
when we're
thinking about goals and what we've achieved over the past year and what we're
hoping
to achieve. Think about us, the ECC and this community and some of the stuff we
've done.
So we want to do a little review. So we've had 11 welcome meetings over the
year. We
have a new Google ad campaign, which we're really happy with. Some of you may
have come
from as a result of that. We've got some new members coming on board. We did,
you know,
sort of draw everything back. We tried to make sure that everything behind the
scenes was
the way that we wanted it to be, the courses, the training, everything else. So
we didn't
advertise for quite a while. And now we feel like we're kind of back. So that's
been really
nice this past year. We had our best performing one, which we're so happy about
. It's so weird
when you're like running something like this with George, I like my best friend
. And we
are genuinely doing this because we love it and we want to share, you know, how
you can
change your life by doing this. So it's weird that there's a financial side to
it as well,
because we're both just doing it because we love it and we want other people to
succeed
and we want to share in it. But to also have had our best performing month, we
're so so
happy with that, because yes, I'm sure many sort of agencies and things they
get ahead
by being a bit cutthroat and maybe not doing things with love like we like to
do. So it's nice
to know that you can do things with love and you can still be okay. Yes, that's
really positive.
We've had 17 training calls and we've had seven photoshoots or socials.
So we've been together quite a lot this year and hopefully even more is to come
this next year as well. Oh, I had some feedback. That was going to write down.
I apologise,
I haven't done that on such a crazy day today. I was going to read back some of
the feedback
that we had. So we did, oh, I'm going to do another one because it was the end.
It was a few months
ago when we did the last one, three months ago. But we did a survey monkey and
with anonymous
feedback to make sure that anyone could say what they wanted to say, that we
wanted to know
what you wanted more of, like what else we could do to improve. As we always do
, but it can be hard
to give that feedback when you're not anonymous. So yeah, we were just so blown
away by the responses,
like they were just so beautiful and so many people saying how their lives have
changed.
And yeah, the friendships they've made, the things they've achieved, we couldn
't believe how
positive it was. So we want to thank you for that. There was a couple of
suggestions. So we,
a couple of people were asking about whether it would be possible for us to
offer other
sites as well as AdultWork. So that is something that we've put a lot of time
into.
As it stands, we haven't been able to find options where it's the money's as
good. The privacy is
there. That's a big one because a lot of these sites can use your content. When
you sign up to
them, you're signing away your content so you can pop up on phone hub or
something like that,
which is a big no-no buzz. So yeah, we've been doing lots of research as a
result of that feedback.
We also did some of our training as a result of the feedback. So we did, I
think there was one
about what was it, like swapping when you want to change your persona. That was
one of the ones
we did. There was two or three that we did that were as a result of things that
people asked for.
So thank you. We always love it. If you've got suggestions on things that you'd
like to know
more about, whether it's webcam, you know, obviously, you know, we want to
prioritise webcam. But
if it's something else, if it's even, you know, something else in life that you
'd like us to try
and deliver them, we will do and we can try and we can get people in now and
again as well to help.
So always give feedback if we can.
Yeah, when you said then that you didn't have it, I was like, I know where
there's some feedback
on here. So I will read out. So somebody said, the process was quick and
helpful and very supportive.
I love the fact that it's ran by women and it's all about empowering each other
.
And another feedback was, I love everything about the ECC. The job is 10 times
more enjoyable
with such an amazing community. It doesn't even feel like work with my girls. I
love you all.
So yeah, they were two very lovely feedbacks we got.
Yeah, so lovely. And I got so many like voice notes over Christmas and stuff
just saying how
people were really happy and, you know, they'd be able to have a nice Christmas
with camera stuff,
which is just the best. Thank you for that, Jean. And yeah, just a few photos.
Our community came
together as we always do. So many events and photo shoots and fun things. As
you can see,
we like dressing up together. Yeah, we found some new shoot location, that new
shoot location with
a hot tub on the penthouse was so nice. And there's loads more.
This was just a small, just picking out a few bits. So it's just loved being
with you this year,
girls. And our goals for this year. So we're sharing with you to keep ourselves
accountable,
some of our goals for this year. So we're looking at like maybe a bit of a
group outing for anyone
that's interested. There's a new thing, they're doing alternative awards for
like performers and
people in the sex work industry. And we're thinking that we're going to submit
ourselves as an agency,
but you can also, you know, submit if you want to, if you want, there are the
categories, if you want
to do it as a webcam performer or content creator or whatever. So we'll keep
you posted about that.
That might be something fun that we can do together, but I'm going to award
ceremony and get dressed up
and have a good night. We are obviously, we're going to do the new survey month
case. So the new
survey is going to be done next week or so. So we'll send you a link to it. You
just click on the
link to it from your phone and there's just a few questions. It's anonymous. So
please, you know,
if you've got any ideas or any, anything at all, anything but good or bad, like
we'd love to hear it.
And we've got this lovely G on the front of which it got me hooked, Mac. So we
have Paul,
our lovely photographer, we're also other photographers that we work with. But
there are
opportunities, if you'd like to be featured in something like this, then please
do let us know,
come to one of our photo shoots and work with one of our photographers and we
can,
we can facilitate this if you're interested in trying to get published in
places. I mean,
do you want to say a bit about that? Yeah, so I've been being published in this
magazine a
couple of times now and they offered me the cover recently and I was definitely
going to do that.
And they, I spoke to them about this community and they would like to put some
of you girls in
the magazine. So yeah, next time up one of our shoots, I think even our
previous shoot out,
if there's images from there, they're happy to put them in the next issue. And
so yeah, so there's
opportunity to be in this magazine, if you girls want to. And so yeah, why not
hey?
And things within the ECC as well. So we hope this year, at least one, that we
will be
recruiting another mentor. So yeah, with quite a few new members coming on,
there's a lot for us
to do, there's a hell of a lot for Sammy to do, bless you Sammy, we love you.
So yeah, it's probably time or, you know, very soon we're going to be looking
for another mentor.
And this will be someone internal, you know, that's just how we like to work.
We like to see our
girls grow, you know, we all started at the same, at the same place. We've all
been there just as
you have. And sort of mentor to the people. And now we're here, and now we have
our
mentors who have come with us from the start. And so yeah, if it's something
that you're
interested in supporting other people through the process, as the wonderful
Sammy does,
then keep your eyes peeled, because we will post details of that in the next
month or so, I imagine.
And that'd be nice to have somebody else on it on the team as well. And of
course, as ever, you
know, we'll be doing all our usual sort of trainings and stuff, trying to think
of what's going to be
best, the best content and training and things for you and socials and photo
shoots. And it's
one of my goals, actually, to bring some more photographers in and work with
some different
photographers. We've been so lucky. We've had we've had a fair few. But I think
the last
couple of phase issues have been quite classic style. And personally, I like
quite alternative
grungy, that sort of thing. So yeah, I'd like to get some new people in and
work with some more
female photographers this year. So that's one of my goals for us all. And if
any of our members are
a photographer, to keep things internal, I wonder if anyone here on this call
or just any of our
members would have a photographer and we could have them come along and do it
too. Yeah, like do
let us know if you or someone you know, just photography. And obviously, we don
't bring anyone
in unless we've usually we've shot with them first, George or I, or we've met
with them, or you know,
obviously, we want to check that they're safe and, you know, all good. But yeah
, we're, it would be
amazing if any of the girls were, maybe we should put that out, actually, maybe
we have to point
yourself out. Yeah, let's talk about that and think about that. And so yeah,
that's going to be
exciting. And some new locations, as always, kind of looking for different
locations and stuff.
And I did post in the group, because I'm thinking about doing the next one in
Nottingham, because
there are quite a few people have asked for one bit further north, because we
've done London for
the last couple of ones. So yeah, I'll keep you posted about that. If anybody f
ancies it, we'll
have a shoot and then I'm sure we'll have some drinks and just, or maybe even
some more wholesome
social time. I don't know, we'll figure it out. But yeah, we'll get together.
And it's always,
even if you've never been to a shoot, please don't be too daunted by it,
because everyone is so
welcoming, honestly. Like, even if you've never been in front of a camera
before, even if you just
come just the first time just to have a look and see, you know, any of the
photographers we work with
are really lovely. I'm always there. Like, I will literally stand next to you
and pose and you can
just copy me if that's how you feel comfortable. Like, we get through it, we
lend each other things,
we're just like, yeah, we just, it's just a nice community feel and we always
have so much fun. So
yeah, if you're thinking about it this year, maybe that could be one of your
goals on your list to
get to a photo shoot. And I think, ah, one last slide. Yeah. So we heard some
top tips. I don't know,
maybe we could, if these are, if these, well, let's have a look, let's see what
they are.
So watch the training videos. Yeah, can't stress this enough. Honestly, the
videos on the
members area of the website are so valuable. Literally, you can just click into
random ones and you
could get so much inspiration and energy. And I think we all have different
favourite ones, but
they go back for so long because all the calls we've ever done are on there
pretty much. So you can
scroll back and back and back and back and back. I think we've only lost a few
over the years.
And women of webcam, I think that was one of my favourites because we heard
loads of members
talking about their personas and how they make it work. And it was quite
diverse and cool to get
inspiration from everyone. But yeah, there's loads. So I'd recommend to do that
. Complete a course,
of course, on the website. There's the courses as well. They're always handy.
Sometimes I just go
and refresh myself, especially with like the DOM course and stuff because it's
good to get those
ideas, isn't it? It's got to hold on to those ideas. Yeah, this has been up, we
wrote this before,
but this has been up in the group for the last few days, hasn't it? So like
getting a love-ense
or something like that so that you can find incentives for them to tick. I love
mine.
Yeah, that's been something that quite a few of our girls did really well with
this year.
That seems to be a bit of a trend for this year, hasn't it? This past year.
So something that I need to do actually, because I haven't actually done that
myself,
I'm going to, that could be one of my goals. I need to figure that out and get
on that.
Find inspiration for your profile. So have a look at the other people on the
website,
if you haven't done already, even if you've already got your persona or you're
quite happy with how
you're doing things or how your profile looks, it never hurts just have a look
through and see
what other people are doing because sometimes you just find one little thing
and you're like,
"Oh yeah, I like that." Talk to other members, of course. You know, feel free
to maybe after this
course, say hello in the group, in the WhatsApp group, you know, if you're open
to be messaged or
whatever, maybe just put a little hello, let other people know. And yeah, set
goals and stay motivated
when it comes to TAN, you know, it's just always helps, doesn't it, to have in
your mind what your
goals are, not just financially, but you know, thinking about the visualization
we did earlier,
the things, the energy that we're welcoming in, the safety, the, you know, the
connection with other
people, the pleasure, you know, whatever it is, just thinking about staying
motivated because of
those things, you know, because that's why we're doing this, isn't it, you know
? And yeah, I think
that's it for me, is there anything you'd add? Well, just about this. Um, no.
Oh, I've got my biggest
tip for sure would be front page or free chat, one or the other, because if you
're just logged on,
especially the new girls who won't be on many people's hot lists, um, it might
be difficult to
get calls through, but if you just pay a couple of credits per hour, you'll be
on the front page.
If you don't want to do that or you don't have credits, you can do free chat,
which also put
you on the front page. For me, this is a game changer. Um, because if you don't
do this, you'll be
somewhere amongst the back pages. And it's hard for people to find you if you
're on the back pages.
So bidding hour by hour, although sometimes you're not going to make the money
back. Of course,
it doesn't happen every hour that you, you know, you're busy. Most of the time
you will. And I do
believe that bidding for the front page or doing free chat to put you on there
does really help.
So that's one of my biggest tips. And also, um, asking, um, your regular
clients, if you're on
their hot lists already, and if not, if they would add you, because being on
more hot lists,
you're more likely to get calls even when you're not on the front page or when
it's not as busy,
because I went online yesterday after some time away. And I had two regular
clients come to me
that I've had for years. And that'll probably, and I wasn't on the front page
because I hadn't had
credit yet to bid myself. But as soon as I logged on, one of my old regulars
came. And that's because
I'm on his hot list and he got the notification to say I was online. So yeah,
making, just asking
your clients if you're on their hot list, or if they want to add you, then, um,
yeah, this can
really help as well. And so yeah, there's two of my tips. Yeah. Thank you. Does
anybody,
before we wrap up for today, does anybody have anything else that they'd like
to share any tips
or any, any thoughts about the call today? Anything else that you'd like to
share? Ladies with each
other or with us. Are we all good? I personally think like I was, I went on
holiday.
And I came back and I was so not motivated to keep working. I made a lot of
money in December and
I was like, maybe I'll just take another week off. I enjoy myself. And then I
logged in and it wasn't
busy. But I was like, I'm already making money. And it is not even busy. So
like I cannot stop.
And having the call today and setting up goals actually, like seeing everyone
so excited and like
with so many life plans, big and small, and seeing that we're all in the same
place,
even like Sammy has a house already, but she also has other things that she
wants to do.
And some of us are just like me, we're just starting. It's like, it's just so
nice to feel like
just we're just all like a big part of the community. And you feel like more
excited of
doing more and being better. It's kind of like a cross feet class.
Yeah.
You don't want to finish, but you're going to do it and it's going to be
amazing. Then you're going
okay, I actually like that. Yeah. Yeah. And you know what's nice? Like being
the person who comes
to the calls and has these goals and stuff and then being on the other side
when you've achieved
a lot of those goals and then new people are coming in and you're like, oh, I
love what I've
achieved. It's so nice. So like you just shift and change and yeah, the
community shifts as well.
Yeah. Again, I want to say thank you girls. This already been changing my life
so far.
And I haven't even been doing for now, even a month. So this is amazing. I'm
really excited.
Thank you. Thank you so much. We are so grateful for every single member.
Honestly,
we are. And you know that we're here. Your mentor is here, but we're also here
like
wearing the chats. You know, if you want to send us a little message, that's
absolutely fine.
And we're still doing it. We're still, we're still coming. We're still doing it
alongside you,
you know. So please send us a little message. Let us know your successes. Let
us know when
you meet one of your goals, even if it's like not having any Washington. You
know, I'm here for it.
And some lovely, some lovely messages in the chat as well. Thank you everybody.
Yeah,
it's been so lovely and wholesome today. Thank you, G, for all your goal
setting and stuff.
Thank you for your contribution to that visualization. Honestly, it was amazing
.
So amazing. And it makes me feel like my goal is going to happen. It's like
makes it feel so real.
So yeah, thank you. And thank you for being here today and shared. Like you
said, like
here and everyone else's stories and energy, it just makes you feel even more
motivated and even
more powerful. That we're all in this together. So yeah, thank you so much, G
ailie, and do share
when you achieve some of your small goals that we said about, just in the know,
keep us motivated
to then achieve our bigger ones. Yeah, thank you very much for having me as
well. I'm really
looking forward to the journey. Thank you. Thank you, Susan. Okay, thank you.
All right, let's have an amazing evening, whatever you're doing. If you're
going on,
have an abundant evening. And yeah, we'll see you very soon at the next, at the
next call.
Okay, thanks guys. Good luck. Bye bye. Thank you.